Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 8: Newspapers 1965-1999, 2004
  - Subseries 1: The Reston Connection, 1981-1995, 2004
    - The Connection-At the CIT: A Leader Takes Charge, October 15, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Capitol Contest, October 22, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Nature Under Siege, October 29, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Representative World Big Victor, November 5, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Best of the West, November 12, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Zoning Under Fire, November 19, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - The Connection, November 26, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Basketball, December 3, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Town Center, December 10, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Workers Who Drink, December 17, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Happy Holidays, December 24, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-The Year In Review and The Year To Come, December 31, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Herndon's One-on-One Mayor: Close Encounters with Rick Thoesen, January 7, 1987 (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Computer Caution: Fairfax Schools Slow Down High-Tech Revolution, January 14, 1987 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Great Scott: Three Local Players Share a Name and a Bright Future, January 21, 1987 (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Housing Pinch: Local Job Boom Putting the Squeeze on Affordable Homes, January 29, 1987 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Do Parole Laws Need Tightening Up? Area Crimes Raise Disturbing Question, February 4, 1987 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-China Syndrome, February 11, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Herndon's Downtown, February 18, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Setting The Balls In Motion, February 25, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-The Intermediate Age: In One Year and Out The Other, March 4, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Saving What's Left, March 11, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Going For The Gold, March 18, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Making Tracks To Dulles, March 25, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Who Holds the Cards?, April 1, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Reston Lands Space Station, April 8, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Growing Pains, April 15, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-When Reston Was Wiehle, April 22, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Merit Pay the Cost?, April 29, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Junkman of Suburbia, May 6, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Three Schools, Three Eras, May 13, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-The Twelve Million Dollar Man, May 20, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Growing Pains, May 27, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-The Doctors Are In, June 3, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Horseplay, June 10, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Heading Into The Future, June 17, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Soccer Mania!, June 24, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-4th of July: What Are We Celebrating?, July 1, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Artists Without A Home, July 8, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-'Don't Fairfax Us': Loudoun Residents Fight Rapid Development, July 15, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-School Bus Scramble, July 22, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Baseball Bonanza, July 29, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Space: Reston's Next Frontier, August 5, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Our Town: The Tourist Mecca You Never Knew, August 12, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Canine Crimefighters, August 19, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Our Roads: Unsafe At Any Speed, August 26, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Bumper To Bumper The Parking Lot Blues, September 2, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-1987 High School Football Preview, September 9, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-That Sinking Feeling, September 16, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-It's 12 O'clock...Do You Know What Your Children Are Eating?, September 23, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Star Attractions George Mason University (GMU) Athletes Break Into Top Ranks, September 30, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-On The Fritz: What's Wrong With Reston Cable, October 7, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Cheek To Cheek: Child Care Comes To High-Tech Row, October 14, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Maggie Reston's No. 1 Nurse, October 21, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Election '87, October 28, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Moving In Moving Up, November 11, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-The Hometown Quiz, November 18, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Polished Brass: Herndon Cops Trade Cowboy Boots For Computers, December 9, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Happy Holidays, December 22, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Best Of The West, December 30, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Scourge Of The Sportscasters, January 6, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-On With The Show, January 13, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Empire: Fairfax Hospital System, January 20, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Not In My Backyard: Group Homes Search For Community Acceptance, January 27, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Another Herndon, February 3, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Good Morning Reston, February 10, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Rising Star, February 17, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Housing Time Bomb: Clock May Be Running Out For Area's Low-Income Residents, February 24, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Building Herndon's Downtown, March 2, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Our Schools Are Falling Apart, March 9, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Reston's Zoo Keeper: Hot Morning DJs Don and Mike Are Alan Goodman's Favorite Pets, March 16, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Under Pressure, March 23, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Franklin Farm No Longer A Frontier Town, March 30, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-The Other Lives Of Allan Rosenbaum, April 6, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Roads Win By A Mile: Voters Approve $150 million Bond By Big Margin, April 13, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-The Battle To Fill Herndon's Top Seat, April 20, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Dads Without Rights: Divorced Fathers Are Kept From Seeing Their Children, April 27, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Sitting Pretty: Herndon Whiz Marty Newsom Eclipses State Gymnastics Record, May 4, 1987 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Our Dollar Hungry Schools, May 11, 1987 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Trial by Fire: Tragedy Tests the Strength of a Family, May 18, 1987 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Far Out: From Test Pilot to Space Expert, June 8, 1987 (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Fertile Crescent: Herndon Parkway Sprouts Hi-Tech Businesses, June 15, 1987 (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Breaking New Ground: Will Reston Town Center Bring Life to Sterile Suburbs?, June 22, 1987 (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Holy Smoke: Father John Heenan A Comfort In Any Crisis, June 29, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-The Evolution Of A Community, July 13, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-The Blueprint Blues: How Growth Is Overwhelming Herndon's Planners, July 20, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Movin' Out: Local Families Flee Suburbia For Life In The Country, July 27, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Nursing Its Wounds: Behind The Breakdown At Cameron Glen Center, August 3, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-At Your Service: Nordstrom Rings Registers, August 0, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Risky Rigs Is That Truck Behind You The One With Faulty Brakes?, August 17, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Chemical Warfare, August 24, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Herndon Chainsaw Massacre, August 31, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Do You Know This Man? (Hint: He Runs Reston), September 7, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Superchurch, September 14, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Shock Waves: In Search Of Top Ratings, Fairfax Radio Station Brings Back Bad Boy Howard Stern, October 12, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Pink Flamingos, October 19, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-'Cut It Out!', October 26, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Election '88, November 2, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Election Results, November 9, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Phenom Of The Opera, November 16, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-They've Been Called Dumb, November 22, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Haven For The Homeless, November 30, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Swinging Into Trouble, December 14, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-A Spot Of Good Cheer To One And All, December 21, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-The Good, The Bad and The Cuddly, December 28, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Recycling, January 4, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Is Reston Association Cracking Up?, January 11, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Sport Or Stunt: Skaters Seek Legitimacy, January 18, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Political Drama: The Man Faces Of Herndon's Les Zidel, January 25, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Still Shaking Things Up: Jack Herrity, February 1, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-No Greater Love, February 8, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Tallyho!, February 15, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Mysterious Explosion Devastates House, February 22, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Knockdown King: David Chalmers, March 1, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Champs: South Lakes Wings Regions, March 8, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Will Nature Strike Out?, March 15, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Skipping School, March 29, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-God And The Thosburns, May 3, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Passion For The Past, June 21, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Cracked Walls Broken Dreams, July 12, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Reston Leader Dies, July 19, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Shop Till You Drop 13 Hours At Fair Oaks Mall, July 26, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Uncle Sam's Cold Hard Cash, August 2, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Sobering Facts, August 9, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-It's Back! Only 3 Weeks Until School Starts!, August 16, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Happy Trails, August 23, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Wanted: Remedies for Top 10 Road Hazards, Auguest 30, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-GRRRRR!! Teams Line Up for '89 Football Season, September 6, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-The Politics of Trees: Environmental Ethic Takes Root in Herndon, September 13, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Blue Devil Heaven: Top Prospect Grant Hill Picks Duke, September 20, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Give Me Shelter: One Woman Leaves Homelessness Behind, September 27, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Next-Door Neighbors: Gateways to the Land of Loudoun, October 4, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-The New British Invasion: Doing Business the English Way, October 11, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Special Election Issue: Men Behind the Money, November 1, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Passage to America: Eastern Tradition Weds Western Culture, November 8, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Cleaning up our Act: Ready or Not, Recycling is Coming, November 15, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Earning His Stripes: For Student Referees, Reston's Chester Gipson..., November 22, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-A Merchant Shows His Brass, November 29, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Caught in a Corner: Fairfax Affluence Is No Shield for Battered Women, December 6, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-The Business of Death: Herndon's J. Berkeley Green..., December 13, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-He's Coming to Town, December 20, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - The Connection-Curtain Call: Local Stars Shine in Best of West, December 27, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - The Connection-They Want to Pump You Up: Fitness Craze Leaves Many on the Sidelines, February 28, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Lifestyles of the Richmond Famous, March 7, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Sunday Best: Area's Black Churches Make a Joyful Noise, March 14, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-The Untouchables: Virginia's magistrates..., March 21, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Who's Special Ed? 'Our kids need to be kids first and disabled second', March 28, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Mug Shots, April 4, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Old Glory: 125 Years After Lee's Surrender, Re-enactors..., April 11, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Earth Day: The clock is ticking, April 18, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Meeting the Challenge: New Reston League opens doors for handicapped kids..., April 25, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Troubled Waters: Will Difficult Run Survive?, May 2, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Political Connections: Kohann Whitney's School Board..., May 9, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Beyond The Basics, May 16, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Grand Finale: Prom Closes Curtain On High School Years, May 23, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Aces, May 30, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-The Great Barrier Beef, June 6, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Forward, March! Five South Lakes Graduates Head to Service Academies, June 13, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Beyond Crystals, June 20, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-It's The Law, June 27, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Backstage At Wolf Trap, July 4, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Happy Campers, July 11, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Safety Net Of Sisters, July 18, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-The Ultimate Gamble, July 25, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-On The Rocks, August 1, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Band On The Run, August 8, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Judgement Day In Traffic Court, August 15, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Home Stretch 5 Tracks Off And Running, August 22, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Schools Prepare For The Ax, August 29, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Terms Of Endurement, September 5, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Call To Duty Gulf Crisis Hits Home, September 12, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-On The Move, September 19, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Elden Street Players, September 26, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Welcome To The Hyatt, October 3, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Pumpkins Aplenty, October 10, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Yes, Virginia, There Is A Race, October 17, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Town Center Makes A Big Splash, October 24, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Your Health Or Your Car, October 31, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Voters Split On Bonds, November 7, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - The Connection-Shopping The World Market, November 14, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Throwing Away The [Latch] Key, November 28, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-The Business Of Recycling, December 5, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Sex Ed: The Calm After The Storm, December 12, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Suite Dreams 'Nutcracker' Brings Sugarplum Visions To Reston, December 19, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Best Of The West, December 27, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-The Inner Workings Of Reston, January 9, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Who Will Be Hurt By State Cuts In Education?, January 16, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-On The Home Front, January 23, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Is Lilla In Trouble?, January 30, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-On The Road To Snow Where, February 6, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-A King For 30 Days, February 13, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Who Will Be Left Behind?, February 20, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Destination Unknown, February 27, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Disabled Workers Find Independence At Opportunities Unlimited, March 6, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - The Connection-Sink Or Swim: Pool Assessments Key Issue In 1991 Reston Association (RA) Election, March 13, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - The Connection-The Changing Face Of High School Sports, March 20, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - The Connection-What Do They Pay?, March 27, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - The Connection-Warning: Turbulence Ahead, April 4, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - The Connection-Redistricting: How Many New Seats For The Fairfax County Board Of Supervisors?, April 10, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - The Connection-Cutting Corners, April 17, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - The Connection-Not As Easy AS It Looks, April 24, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-The Soccer Boomers, May 1, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Hyatt: Serving Town Center And The Reston Community, May 8, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-F.I.S.H. Local Charitable Group Reels In The Needy, May 15, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-A Grave Man, Indeed, May 22, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Everybody Pays, Not Everybody Plays, May 29, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Cutting Class, June 5, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-That's My Dad, June 12, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Air Time, Jun 19, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Main Event: St. Audrey and Tom Terrific Prepare For The Mother Of All Elections, June 26, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Still Pumpin', July 3, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Who makes What On Herndon's Payroll?, July 10, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-For The Rich, Famous and Secluded, July 17, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Let's Get Trashed, July 24, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Hat Tricked: Norther Virginia Soccer Teams Lose National Title Bids In Omatha, July 31, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - The Connection-Handle With Care, August 7, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-7 Great Sporting Adventures, August 14, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-For Local Seniors, August 21, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Silent Movement: Herndon's Diversity Grows As Hispanic Population Swells, August 28, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-Discover Reston, September 4, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Birth Of An Industry, September 11, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Face Off: Audrey Moore, Tom Davis Field Questions On Issues In County Board Chair Race, September 18, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Years Of Theater, September 25, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Charlie Allen's Mission, October 2, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Back In The Saddle, October 9, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-We're 10 Years Old, October 16, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Still Teaching: 100 Year Old Lula Fones Disappointed In Today's Education, October 23, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Good Buys, November 13, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Festive Spirit, December 4, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Rudolph Leads The Way To New Village Center At Dulles, December 11, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - The Connection-Spirited Display, December 18, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - The Connection-A Little Encouragement: GTE Government Systems Gives Extra Perks To mass Transit Commuters, December 27, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - The Connection-True Test: Centreville District's New Supervisor Excited By Challenges, January 8, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-Bold Art For Grace, January 15, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-Greatest Hits, January 22, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Hail To The Redskins, January 29, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - The Connection-High Standards, February 5, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - The Connection-Tales Of The Recession, February 12, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - The Connection-Amazing Feat, February 24, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - The Connection-Connecting With Art, March 4, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - The Connection-Comeback Kids, March 11, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - The Connection-Learning The Ropes: Howell Completes Her First General ASsembly SEssion, January 8, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - The Connection-Real Honor: Seahawks Coach Byrd, March 25, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - The Connection-Best Of Reston, April 1, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - The Connection-Parent Power, April 8, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - The Connection-Cable Access Comes Of Age, April 15, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - The Connection-Split Personality: Herndon's Nathaniel Green Combines Preaching And Police Work, April 22, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - The Connection-Pension Whirlpool, April 29, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - The Connection-Reston memories, May 6, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - The Connection-International Exchange, May 13, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - The Connection-Fun And Games: Reston Festival, May 20, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - The Connection-Skinflint's Guide, May 27, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - The Connection-Bring The War Home From China Beach To Herndon, June 3, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - The Connection-In A Hole: Stuart Finley Searches Desperately For Water Leaks, June 10, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - The Connection-Free At Last!, June 17, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - The Connection-It's A Mad, Mad Sports World, June 24, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - The Connection-Celebrating Fairfax, July 8, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - The Connection-The Goose With The Golden Egg?, July 15, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - The Connection-In The Swim: County Adapts Recreation For The Disabled, July 22, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - The Connection-Living In Harmony, July 29, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 4)